Benjamin Vølund

Software Engineer

</> benjaminvoelund.dev

Silkeborg, Denmark

% +45 26 15 90 59

bvoelund@hotmail.com



EDUCATION

Engineer in Softwaretechnologies

Aarhus Universitet, 2018 – now

Bachelor degree as a Software Engineer at Aarhus University

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer @ Jysk

Aug. 2021 - Present

 \rightarrow Been part of developing multiple frontend systems - primarily a modern cash register system for the company stores, using React.

Internship @ Kamstrup

Feb. 2020 - Jun. 2020

 \rightarrow Internship as part of my education. Got to work on my own project from the ground up, in the shape of a WPF Application in C#.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

TypeScript, JavaScript, CSS/Sass, HTML, C#, Cypress, Jest, Redux, GraphQL, MongoDB

Frameworks & Libraries

 \rightarrow React, NodeJs, TailwindCSS, .NET

ABOUT ME

My name is Benjamin Vølund and I'm a experienced Software Engineer, and have worked primarily with development of frontend applications over the last couple of years. In my sparetime I enjoy basically anything nerdy, from coding sparetime project, gaming, to building with Lego bricks.

